http://richardsondavis.com/privacy-policy/

Contact Us
Terms of Use
Privacy Notice
Privacy Policy
Snyder Funeral Homes, Inc. is deeply committed to protecting the privacy of our website visitors. Read below to find out about our official privacy policy.  This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for Snyder Funeral Homes, Inc. (www.SnyderFuneralHomes.com) and applies to all information collected by this web site.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request (e.g. to ship an order).
Unless you ask us not to, we might contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
Your Access to and Control Over Information
By contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website you may:
See what data we have about you, if any.
Change/correct any data we have about you.
Have us delete any data we have about you.
Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
Opt out of any future contact from us.
Security
We take precautions to protect your information both online and offline.  Any and all submissions remain confidential.
When you submit sensitive information on our site (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this (on ours and any webpage) by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the web page.
To protect your information offline, only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at (419) 884-1711.
Digital Millennium Copyright Act Policy
Digital Media Policy
Snyder Funeral Homes never intentionally uses copyrighted material.  In the event that a user submits content that you believe to be copyrighted and the user does not have a license to use the material, please follow the procedure outlined below.
Notice and Takedown Procedure
It is our policy to quickly respond to notices of alleged copyright infringement that comply with the United States Digital Millennium Copyright Act (DMCA). This page describes the information that should be included in these notices. It is designed to make submitting notices of alleged infringement to the Digital Media Law Project (the “DMLP”) as straightforward as possible while reducing the number of notices that we receive that are fraudulent or difficult to understand or verify. The form of notice specified below is consistent with the form suggested by the DMCA (the text of which can be found at the U.S. Copyright Office Web Site, http://www.copyright.gov), but we will respond to notices of this form from other jurisdictions as well.
It is expected that all users of any part of the DMLP site will comply with applicable copyright laws. However, if the DMLP receives proper notification of claimed copyright infringement, our response to these notices will include removing or disabling access to material claimed to be the subject of infringing activity and/or terminating subscribers, regardless of whether we may be liable for such infringement under United States law or the laws of another jurisdiction.
If we remove or disable access in response to such a notice, we will make a good-faith attempt to contact the owner or administrator of the affected site or content so that they may make a counter notification pursuant to Sections 512(g)(2) and (3) of the DMCA. We may also document notices of alleged infringement on which we act.
Designated Agent
The DMLP’s Designated Agent to receive notification of alleged infringement under the DMCA is: Hannah Snyder
Email: hannah@snyderfuneralhomes.com
Physical Mail: P.O. Box 3085, Mansfield, Ohio 44904
Upon receipt of proper notification of claimed infringement, the DMLP will follow the procedures outlined herein and in the DMCA.
Infringement Notification
If you believe that your work has been copied in a way that constitutes copyright infringement, or your intellectual property rights have been otherwise violated, please provide the DMLP’s Registered Agent (listed above) the following information in a written communication (preferably via email):
Identification of the copyrighted work claimed to have been infringed, or, if multiple copyrighted works at a single online site are covered by a single notification, a representative list of such works at that site; Identification of the material that is claimed to be infringing or to be the subject of infringing activity and that is to be removed or access to which is to be disabled, and information reasonably sufficient to permit the DMLP to locate the material; Information reasonably sufficient to permit the DMLP to contact the complaining party, such as an address, telephone number, and, if available, an email address at which the complaining party may be contacted; The following statement: “I have a good faith belief that use of the material in the manner complained of is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law”; The following statement: “I swear, under penalty of perjury, that the information in the notification is accurate, and that I am the copyright owner or am authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed”; and A physical or electronic signature of the owner or a person authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed. Please note that you may be liable for damages (including costs and attorneys’ fees) if you materially misrepresent that material is infringing your copyrights. Accordingly, if you are not sure whether material available online infringes your copyright, we suggest that you first contact an attorney.
Counter Notification
A provider of content subject to a claim of infringment may make a counter notification pursuant to sections 512(g)(2) and (3) of the DMCA. To file a counter notification with us, please provide the DMLP’s Registered Agent (listed above) the following information in a written communication (preferably via email):
Identification of the material that has been removed or to which access has been disabled and the location at which the material appeared before it was removed or access to it was disabled; Your name, address, and telephone number; The following statement: “I consent to the jurisdiction of Federal District Court for the [insert the federal judicial district in which your address is located]”; The following statement: “I will accept service of process from [insert the name of the person who submitted the infringement notification] or his/her agent”; The following statement: “I swear, under penalty of perjury, that I have a good faith belief that the affected material was removed or disabled as a result of a mistake or misidentification of the material to be removed or disabled”; and
Your signature, in physical or electronic form. Upon receipt of such counter notification, the DMLP will promptly provide the person who provided the original infringement notification with a copy of the counter notification, and inform that person that the DMLP will replace the removed material or cease disabling access to it in 10 business days. DMLP will replace the removed material and cease disabling access to it not less than 10, nor more than 14, business days following receipt of the counter notice, unless our Designated Agent first receives notice from the person who submitted the original infringement notification that such person has filed an action seeking a court order to restrain the subscriber from engaging in infringing activity relating to the material on our system or network.
Repeat Infringers
In accordance with Section 512(i)(1)(a) of the DMCA, the DMLP will, in appropriate circumstances, disable and/or terminate the accounts of users who are repeat infringers.
Accommodation of Standard Technical Measures
It is the DMLP’s policy to accommodate and not interfere with standard technical measures used by copyright owners to identify or protect copyrighted works that the DMLP determines are reasonable under the circumstances.
